ecpulse.com 2009-09-27

# Privacy Policy , Company Profile - ecPulse.com

---  
  
|   
---  
|  |  | 

|  Breaking News  |  |   
---|---|---  
  
Privacy Policy  
  
The privacy policy published on this page will be applied to all users of ecPulse.com (“Company”, “we”, “website”). ecPulse.com cordially respects the privacy rights of its users and visitors and committed to ensuring their online privacy, and you do not accept this policy, we kindly ask you not to use this website in order to avoid any conflict. As a user (“visitor”, “client”, “you”), when you enter our website it implicitly means that you have read and accepted our privacy policy published on this page. This privacy policy applies.

Non-Personal Information  
  
ecPulse.com guarantees the privacy of all visitors of the website. Every once in a while, the company may provide data to a third party, but only for general statistics regarding the number of users of the website and for marketing campaigns. These statistics will not include any personal information about the website users.

We use a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you visit our Web site. This company may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visit to this website in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

Personal Information  
  
Users have to submit personal information that you voluntary provide like Name, Postal Address, Phone number, E-mail for us to answer all their questions and inquiries. This information will only be used to contact users/visitors of the website in order to answer their questions and inquiries, as well as to inform them about the services and the instruments that the company will offer in the future.

Privacy  
  
ecPulse.comwould like to draw your attention on the fact that we use the best technological methods and means to maintain the privacy of the personal information of the website users. However, there is no comprehensive protection system that offers full protection for personal information, thus making it vulnerable to hacking.

Links and Advertisements to Third-Party Web Sites  
  
ecPulse.com may provide advertisements (“ads”) and/or links to third-party websites (“them”). Since we do not control the material displayed, services and/or the third-party website we are not responsible for any information that you provide to them or any further communication and agreements that you will hold with them, we hold ourselves non liable for any further communication between you and them. We recommend and encourage you to read the privacy policies on the third-party’s website.

Underage Visitors

People that are below 18 years are not allowed to send any information or data to the company. Nor are they allowed to do any legal action on the website ofecPulse.com.

Modifications

We reserve the rights to amend, change and/or alter the content of this privacy policy at anytime by posting revisions on this page. The posted changes shall be effective upon posting.  
| 

|   
---  
  
Note: Our website content is subject to errors, changes and updates; the use of the websites constitutes your acceptance of our [Privacy Policy](http://www.ecpulse.com/en/companyprofile/privacypolicy/ "Privacy Policy") and [Risk Disclosure](http://www.ecpulse.com/en/companyprofile/riskdisclosure/ "Risk Disclosure")  
Risk Disclaimer: The content of ecPulse.com and any page in the website contain information for investors/traders and is not a recommendation to buy or sell currencies, stocks, gold, silver & energies, nor an offer to buy or sell currencies, stocks, gold, silver & energies. The information provided reflects the writers' opinions that deemed reliable but is not guaranteed as to accuracy or completeness. ecPulse is not liable for any losses or damages, monetary or otherwise that result. I recommend that anyone trades currencies, stocks, gold, silver & energies should do so with caution and consult with a broker before doing so. Prior performance may not be indicative of future performance. Currencies, stocks gold, silver &energies presented should be considered speculative with a high degree of volatility and risk.  
© 2008 ecPulse.com All Rights Reserved
